<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<objects name="Object Load" version="0.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<object type="Scenario" name="">
		<property name="strContentPackName" value="Modern Europe"/>
		<property name="strName" value="Rise of an Empire"/>
		<property name="strDisplayName" value="Rise of an Empire"/>
		<property name="strDescription" value="1861, South Carolina and other states cede from the United States. By 1863, the South convinces Britain and France that cotton is king, and receive minimal support from British and French forces under condition of the end of slavery by 1885. The CSA won the American Civil War, and successfully ceded from the USA. They chose not to occupy the North, nor bring the North under their control, as they were only fighting for their freedom, from the industrialist way of life that had overcome Washington and the North, in stark contrast to the agriculturalist ideals of the South and a different way of life. The CSA expands to the west, and through their own manifest destiny draw up plans for war with Mexico in order to claim its north regions as their own. Tijuana becomes their port on the Pacific after the successful triumph over Mexican forces south of Texas and the Arizona territory. In 1875, the CSA begins the integration of slaves into normal society, but restricting their freedom through the use of Jim Crow laws. Many chose to defect to Spanish controlled Cuba or Puerto Rico. Come 1898, the CSS Arkansas blows up in Havana, causing the CSA to declare war on Spain. The CSA takes control of Spanish Caribbean holdings, and wins key battles against the Spanish navy. Having no presence in the Pacific to matter, the Philippines remain under Spanish control. The Spanish offer peace to the CSA, which is accepted under condition that half of the remaining Spanish navy gets turned over to the CSA so that it can protect its new Caribbean holdings. The turn of the century brings upon the Panama Canal project from the United States in order to link the east coast to the west coast, far reducing sailing times, but bringing Northern shipping through Southern controlled waters. 1912 sees Cuba admitted to the CSA as a state, and 1913 sees Puerto Rico join them. The First World War breaks out in Europe, and eventually the Zimmerman Note makes its way into Confederate hands. When the CSA sees the Entente's plans to bring Mexico into the war to stop American goods from reaching the Allied powers (long time customers of Southern goods and Northern weapons) and bring historical lands back under Mexican control from the western CSA, the CSA declares war on the Entente, joining their former Civil War allies in a fight against Germany. The United States, seeing their Southern brethren building a grand army and navy decide to join the war effort as well, and try to reduce the tensions the two nations have had since the 1860's by fighting side by side once again. The Allied powers win the war in Europe as more than a million American soldiers join the front lines, mostly Negro soldiers from the South. After the war, the United States goes into a state of relative economic growth as it generates strong trade ties with the South. Racial issues in the South begin to take over politics throughout the late 1920's, and by the time the US stock market crashes in 1929, bringing down the CS market with it, a fascist revolution takes over the South. Negros become second class citizens by Constitutional amendment, soon expanded to Mexican and Latin American descendants. The South gives rise to the idea of a Master Race similar to the ideas of the rising National Socialist Workers' Party in Germany. Tensions with the US have risen to heights last seen right after the Civil War as trade with the US in the midst of depression has all but ceased, as well as the promotion that all men are equal in the United States. To try to bring balance back to the US economy, the US institutes new socialist measures to help realize the dream of equality and bread on the table for all. The newly elected Roosevelt brings with him a new socialist government under the Communist Party to address the social unrest within the USA. Wrought with internal struggles, relations with European nations begin to fade for the CSA, while the USA finds a new ally in Moscow and the Red goverment of Stalin. How will the American nations handle a Second World War, one in which their own ideals are being fought for across the European landscape?"/>
		<property name="strVersion" value="0.5.0"/>
		<property name="fileGame" value="game.xml"/>
		<property name="nTurnDuration" value="1"/>
		<property name="nScenarioDuration" value="676"/>
		<property name="nStartYear" value="1933"/>
		<property name="nStartDay" value="30"/>
		<property name="dateStart" value="01/30/1933"/>
		<property name="dateEnd" value="01/14/1946"/>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="0"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedData.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="2"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - AI"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataAI.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="3"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - ROTR"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataROTR.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="4"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Historic Countries"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataHistoricCountries.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="5"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Unit Templates"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataUnitTemplates.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="6"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Factories"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataFactories.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="7"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Research"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataResearch.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="8"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Templates"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataTemplates.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="9"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Unit Template Sprites"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataUnitTemplateSprites.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="SharedDataFileRef" name="objSharedDataFileRefs">
			<property name="nFileRefID" value="10"/>
			<property name="bScenario" value="true"/>
			<property name="strFileLoadName" value="Shared Data - Culture Templates"/>
			<property name="fileSharedData" value="sharedDataCultureTemplates.xml"/>
		</object>
		<object type="ScenarioDisplaySettings" name="objDisplaySettings">
			<property name="strMapName" value="World"/>
			<property name="strSpriteLibName" value="World"/>
			<property name="strSpriteMapName" value=""/>
			<property name="strMapViewsName" value="UnifiedMapViews"/>
			<property name="strLightingGroupName" value="BasicLighting"/>
			<property name="strCameraSettingsName" value="WorldUnified"/>
			<property name="fileMapProperties" value="/../Modern Europe/system/DisplayLibraries/Maps/World/xml/properties.xml"/>
		</object>
	</object>
</objects>
